<LESSON>

<HEADINGS>
	<1>Ready? Place your hands as described in the sidebar and type:</1>
	<2>Good work! Now let's learn the D key. Type the following:</2>
	<3>Good! Now let's learn the semi-colon and F key.</3>
	<4>Nice work! Now let's move on to the F key.</4>
	<5>Swell! Now let's combine all those.</5>
	<6>Now let's add the J and K keys.</6>
	<7>Next, add the K key.</7>
	<8>Finally, let's add the L key.</8>
</HEADINGS>

             
<DESCRIPTION>This lesson will teach you basic hand positions. Rest your left hand fingers on "ASDF" and place the right hand fingers on "JKL;". Your right thumb should be resting above the space bar.</DESCRIPTION>

<LessonTime>-1</LessonTime>
<MaxErrors>-1</MaxErrors>
<MinWPM>-1</MinWPM>
<MinAccuracy>-1</MinAccuracy>

<TASK>
<HEADING>1</HEADING>
<TEXT>aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa aaa</TEXT>
<TEXT>aaa sss aaa sss aaa sss aaa sss aaa sss aaa sss aaa</TEXT>
<TEXT>ddd ddd ddd ddd ddd ddd asd asd asd asd asd asd</TEXT>
<TEXT>add add add add add add add add add add add add</TEXT>
</TASK>

<TASK>
<HEADING>3</HEADING>
<TEXT>;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;; ;;;</TEXT>
<TEXT>add dads; add dads; add dads; add dads; add dad;</TEXT>
<TEXT>fff fff fff fff fff fff fff asdf asdf asdf asdf asdf asdf</TEXT>
<TEXT>aff aff aff aff aff aff aff aff aff aff aff aff aff aff aff</TEXT>
</TASK>

<TASK>
<HEADING>6</HEADING>
<TEXT>jjj jjj jjj jjj jjj jjj jjj asj asj asj asj asj asj asj asj asj</TEXT>
<TEXT>jsd jsd jsd jsd jsd jsd jsd jsd jsd jsf jsf jsf jsf jsf jsf</TEXT>
<TEXT>fak fak fak fak fak fak fak fak sak sak sak sak sak sak</TEXT>
<TEXT>dak; dak; dak; dak; dak; dak; dak; dak; dak; dak; dak;</TEXT>
</TASK>

<TASK>
<HEADING>8</HEADING>
<TEXT>lll lll lll lll lll lll lll lll lll jal jal jal jal jal jal jal jal jal</TEXT>
<TEXT>lad lad lad lad lad lad lad lad lass lass lass lass lass</TEXT>
<TEXT>sal sal sal sal sal sal sal sal sal fal fal fal fal fal fal fal</TEXT>
<TEXT>lass; lad; lass; lad; lass; lad; lass; lad; lass; lad; lass;</TEXT>
</TASK>


</LESSON>
